Contact

rachel.gamble@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rachelgamble-rn-bsn-a6b01bb0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medical Devices
Training
Clinical Specialists

Languages
Sign Languages

Rachel Gamble, RN, BSN

Clinical Specialist at Lumicell - Oncology Houston, Texas

Summary

Clinical Specialist with over 8 years of healthcare industry experience. Specialized in implementing clinical solutions for start-up medical device companies in the oncology, critical care, and surgical sectors. Proficient in identifying, training, and supporting hospitals and physicians across multiple disciplines. Provide guidance to sales professionals and manage distributor teams ranging from 5-30 people per group placing great emphasis on creating and upholding exceptional communication and interpersonal relations that yield consistent, positive results.

Core competencies include: Medical Device, Surgical Device, Education, Oncology, Account Management, Case Support, Clinical Trials, Critical Care, Complex Sales, Interpersonal Communication, Live Training, Webinars, Team Management, Sales Support, Distributors, Lead Generation, Networking, Account Expansion, Creation of Educational Materials, Presentations, Increase Profits, Hospital Implementation.

Experience

Lumicell
Clinical Specialist
February 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Pinnacle Biologics, Inc.
Photodynamic Therapy (PDT) Specialist 2018 - 2019 (1 year)
Houston, Texas Area

South territory

Attune Medical Clinical Specialist 2017 - 2018 (1 year) Western and Midwestern territories

iovera
Clinical Specialist - Clinical Account Manager
2016 - 2017 (1 year)
Houston, Texas

Southeast territory

FlexCare Medical Staffing Travel RN II, BSN, CCRN 2014 - 2015 (1 year) Orange County, California Area

General, Neuro, and Cardiovascular ICU units

Texas Health Harris Methodist Fort Worth RN II, BSN, CCRN 2013 - 2014 (1 year) Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Interventional and diagnostic Cardiac Cath Lab - First Responder STEMI Team

Parkland Hospital RN, BSN, CCRN June 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 7 months) Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Surgical/Trauma Neuro ICU

Education

Stephen F. Austin State University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Critical Care Nursing · (2009 - 2011)